Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - P
        - Prisoners of Technology - Volume 8, 1998; SR-28321; Prisoners of Technology (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28322. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FK 008; A-side Matrix # Music House FK08A1
          Fresh Kutt Records
        - Prisoners of Technology - Volume 8, 1998; SR-28322; Prisoners of Technology (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28321. 2 copies. Annotated.
        - Private Eye - Hot girl, 1983; SR-28323; Private Eye (Box 397)
          Catalog # D-213; A-side Matrix # P D 213 A
        - Private P - Informer, 1993; SR-28324; Private P; Original Kappa Donner (Box 397)
          Catalog # TY-075; A-side Matrix # INFORMER VP-PS/CM TY-075-A
          Tan-Yah
        - Private Possession - Are you wid it, 1986; SR-28325; Private Possession; Hunter Hayes (Box 397)
          Catalog # PRO-423; A-side Matrix # A- PRO-423-A
        - Prizm & Eclipse - Scream, 1999; SR-28326; Prizm & Eclipse (Box 397)
          Catalog # BAS 001; A-side Matrix # 9902X35A Scream A+Z S6
          Bad Ass Shit!
        - Probe1 - Intake; 52DSL, 2005; SR-28327; Probe1; Crackhead Worm (Box 397)
          Catalog # TRS003; A-side Matrix # 58307 1A IRS 03
          Torsion Records
        - Process And The Doo Rags - I promise to remember, 1987; SR-28328; Process And The Doo Rags (Box 397)
          Catalog # 44 6021; A-side Matrix # XSS-175665-1BDMM G1
        - Process And The Doo Rags - Call me up, 1987; SR-28329; Process And The Doo Rags (Box 397)
          Catalog # 44 06840; A-side Matrix # STERLING XSS 176125 1A G1 A4
        - Process And The Doo Rags - Too sharp, 1985; SR-28330; Process And The Doo Rags (Box 397)
          Catalog # CAS 2081; A-side Matrix # STERLING P-AP XSS-174370-1A
        - Prodigy - The fat of the land (Disc one), 1997; SR-28331; Prodigy (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28332. Double album.
          Catalog # XLLP 121; A-side Matrix # MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE XLLP 121 A1 DAMONT
          XL Recordings
        - Prodigy - The fat of the land (Disc two), 1997; SR-28332; Prodigy (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28331. Double album.
          Catalog # XLLP 121; A-side Matrix # XLLP 121 C1 MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE DAMONT
        - Prodigy - Firestarter, 1996; SR-28333; Prodigy (Box 397)
          Catalog # XLT 70; A-side Matrix # DAMONT MIKE'S THE EXCHANGE XLT 70 A
        - Prodigy - Baby's got a temper, 2002; SR-28334; Prodigy (Box 397)
          Catalog # 0-42456; A-side Matrix # 0-42456-A SR-1 Future Disc
          Maverick
        - Professor - Big belly ermine, 1984; SR-28335; Professor (Box 397)
          Catalog # PB 15; A-side Matrix # B-1-PB15A-RE
          Cocoa Records
        - Professor Griff - Pawns in the game, 1990; SR-28336; Professor Griff; Last Asiatic Disciples (Box 397)
          Catalog # XR-111; A-side Matrix # GR-150-A IN GOD WE TRUST FULLERSOUND NH
          Luke SkyyWalker Records
        - Professor Griff - Pawns in the game, 1990; SR-28337; Professor Griff; Last Asiatic Disciples (Box 397)
          Catalog # GR 131; A-side Matrix # FULLERSOUND MT GR-131-A IN GOD WE TRUST
          Skyywalker Records
        - Professor Trance - Shaman's breath, 1995; SR-28338; Professor Trance; Energisers (Box 397)
          Catalog # PR12 6915-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 6915-1-AS-HS
        - Professor X - What's up g?, 1991; SR-28339; Professor X (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28340. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 162-440 532-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-532-1 A SP DMS cg
        - Professor X - What's up g?, 1991; SR-28340; Professor X (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28339. 2 copies.
        - Professor X - Years of the 9, on the blackhand side, 1990; SR-28341; Professor X (Box 397)
          Catalog # 440 522-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-522-1 A-SP 1-1 DMS cg
        - Professor X - Years of the 9, on the blackhand side, 1990; SR-28342; Professor X (Box 397)
        - Professor X - Years of the 9, on the blackhand side, 1990; SR-28343; Professor X (Box 397)
        - Professor X - They don't know jack, 1993; SR-28344; Professor X (Box 397)
          Catalog # 859 027-1; A-side Matrix # 422-859-027-1 A
        - Professor X - They don't know jack, 1993; SR-28345; Professor X (Box 397)
        - Professor X - They don't know jack, 1993; SR-28346; Professor X (Box 397)
        - Professor X - 3 joints (before the dawn of the veiled marauder), 1999; SR-28347; Professor X; Clinton, George (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28348. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ECHO 2335; A-side Matrix # ECHO2335-A DCHARLES
          Echo International
        - Professor X - 3 joints (before the dawn of the veiled marauder), 1999; SR-28348; Professor X; Clinton, George (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28347. 2 copies.
        - Profyle - I ain't the one, 1999; SR-28349; Profyle (Box 397)
          Catalog # U12-56241-RE1; A-side Matrix # U12-56241RE2 A
        - Profyle - I ain't the one, 1999; SR-28350; Profyle (Box 397)
        - Program 2 Beltram - The omen, 1991; SR-28352; Program 2 Beltram (Box 397)
          Catalog # RS 9136; A-side Matrix # FOON MASTERINE RS 9136 A1
          R&S Records
        - Progression - Tom-Tom, 1986; SR-28353; Progression (Box 397)
          Catalog # SRC 31800; A-side Matrix # SRC31800A
          SRC Records
        - Progressive Sounds of South - Miami breaks volume one, 1996; SR-12897; Progressive Sounds of South; P.S.S. (Box 397)
          Catalog # CST2T; A-side Matrix # CST-02 T M
          Coast
        - Project - Love Rescue, 1981; SR-28358; Project (Box 397)
          Catalog # PBI-1001; A-side Matrix # PBI-1001
          P.B.I. Records
        - Project Demolition - Kik it in your crib, 1988; SR-28351; Project Demolition (Box 397)
          Catalog # EN-6042; A-side Matrix # EN6042-A DCHARLES
        - Project Pat - Represent it, 1999; SR-28354; Project Pat (Box 397)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0941; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0941A MB
          Relativity
        - Project Pat - Goldshine, 1999; SR-28355; Project Pat; Three 6 Mafia (Box 397)
          Catalog # RPROLP 4337; A-side Matrix # RPROLP 4337A RE2 MB
          Loud Records
        - Project Pat - Goldshine, 1999; SR-28356; Project Pat; Three 6 Mafia (Box 397)
        - Promatic - Promatic, 2003; SR-28357; Promatic; Slim Shady (Box 397)
          Catalog # AV 282; A-side Matrix # AV-282-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 66952 DON GROSSINGER
          AV8
        - Propellerheads - Decksandrumsandrockandroll (Disc one), 1998; SR-28359; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28360. Double album.
          Catalog # WALL LP 015; A-side Matrix # MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE WALL LP 015-A1
          Wall of Sound
        - Propellerheads - Decksandrumsandrockandroll (Disc two), 1998; SR-28360; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28359. Double album.
          Catalog # WALL LP 015; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 015-C1 MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE
        - Propellerheads - Decksandrumsandrockandroll (Disc one), 1998; SR-28361; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28362. Double album.
        - Propellerheads - Decksandrumsandrockandroll (Disc two), 1998; SR-28362; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28361. Double album.
        - Propellerheads - History repeating, 1997; SR-28363; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          Catalog # WALLT 036; A-side Matrix # MIKE'S - THE EXCHANGE WALL T 036-A1
        - Propellerheads - Bang on!, 1998; SR-28364; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          Catalog # WALL T 039; A-side Matrix # SIMON - THE EXCHANGE WALL T 39-A1
        - Propellerheads - Spybreak!, 1997; SR-28365; Propellerheads (Box 397)
          Catalog # WALLT 029; A-side Matrix # SIMON- THE EXCHANGE WALLT029-A1
        - Proper Dos - Tales from the westside, 1994; SR-28366; Proper Dos (Box 397)
          Catalog # PRO 1102-1; A-side Matrix # HUB TV Herbie JR PRO-1102-1-A
        - Proper Dos - Tales from the westside, 1994; SR-28367; Proper Dos (Box 397)
          Catalog # PRO 1102-1; A-side Matrix # Herbie Jr PRO-1102-1-A
        - Proper Utensils - That's enuff! (Disc one), 1998; SR-28368; Proper Utensils (Box 397)
          Catalog # LU722-1; A-side Matrix # LU-722-1-A EUROPA DISK DMM NY USA 28238
        - Proper Utensils - That's enuff! (Disc two), 1998; SR-28369; Proper Utensils (Box 397)
        - Proper Utensils - Just funnin' (Disc two), 1995; SR-28370; Proper Utensils (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28371. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MOB4518-1; A-side Matrix # MOB-4518-1-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 12719
          Mob Records & Tapes
        - Proper Utensils - Just funnin' (Disc two), 1995; SR-28371; Proper Utensils (Box 397)
          In same jacket as # SR-28370. 2 copies.
        - Proper Utensils - Go go rump shaker, 1993; SR-28372; Proper Utensils (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28373. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MOB4517-1; A-side Matrix # MOB-4517-1 A (REM)
        - Proper Utensils - Go go rump shaker, 1993; SR-28373; Proper Utensils (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28372. 2 copies.
        - Prophet Jones - Woof; I know you wanna, 2001; SR-28374; Prophet Jones (Box 398)
          Catalog # 440 015 026-1; A-side Matrix # 440-015-026-1A STERLING
        - Prophets Of Da City - Universal Souljaz (Disc two), 1995; SR-28375; Prophets Of Da City (Box 398)
          Catalog # NATLP 54; A-side Matrix # SIMON - THE EXCHANGE NATLP 54
          Nation Records
          London, England
        - Prozack Turner - Wonderful life, 2003; SR-28376; Prozack Turner (Box 398)
          Catalog # DRMR-14149-1; A-side Matrix # DRMR-14149-1-A
        - Prozack Turner - Wonderful life, 2003; SR-28377; Prozack Turner (Box 398)
        - Pryor, Richard - Rev. Du Rite, 1981; SR-28378; Pryor, Richard (Box 398)
          Catalog # LAFF A216; A-side Matrix # S8465 SIDE 1
          Laff Records
        - Pryor, Richard - Richard Pyror meets ... Richard & Willie and ... the S.L.A.!!, 1976; SR-28379; Pryor, Richard; Richard & Willie (Box 398)
          Catalog # LAFF A188; A-side Matrix # LAFF 188-A S-4744
        - Prysock, Arthur - Here's to good friends, 1978; SR-28380; Prysock, Arthur (Box 398)
          Catalog # MCA-3061; A-side Matrix # MCA 1559 W2
        - Pseudo Slang - Broke & copasetic; Yes doubt; Snowy daze again, 2006; SR-28382; Pseudo Slang; Mojica, Vinia (Box 398)
          Catalog # FB 2526; A-side Matrix # FB 2526 A
          Fat Beats
        - PSO - Nxt 2u, 1987; SR-28383; PSO (Box 398)
          Catalog # RTR-815; A-side Matrix # RTR-815-B-A FULLERSOUND
          RTR Records
        - Psyche Origami - At last, 2004; SR-28381; Psyche Origami (Box 398)
          Catalog # PSY-ALST-777; A-side Matrix # 57956E1/A RECORDPRESSING.COM PSY-ALST-777 A
          ArcTheFinger Records
        - Psychedelic Furs - Here come cowboys, 1984; SR-28384; Psychedelic Furs (Box 398)
          Catalog # AS 1908; A-side Matrix # P XSM-169741-1A
        - Psycho Realm - Stone garden, 1997; SR-28385; Psycho Realm (Box 398)
          Catalog # CAS 3384; A-side Matrix # XSS3384A2 AABAJ
        - Psycho Realm - Psycho city blocks, 1997; SR-28386; Psycho Realm (Box 398)
          Catalog # 44 78573; A-side Matrix # XSS-78573A-1A RJ
        - Psycho Realm - The stone garden, 1997; SR-28387; Psycho Realm (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28388. Different discs.
          Catalog # 44 78727; A-side Matrix # XSS-78727A-1B RJ
        - Psycho Realm - Psycho city blocks, 1997; SR-28388; Psycho Realm (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28387. Different discs.
        - Psycho Team - Bolero (the remix), 1991; SR-28389; Psycho Team (Box 398)
          Catalog # DW 1919; A-side Matrix # DW1919-A
          Bologna, Italy
        - Psychotron - Free, 1993; SR-28390; Psychotron (Box 398)
          Catalog # NLX 132; A-side Matrix # NLX-132-A
          No Limits
          Milan, Italy
        - Psyclone - Trife, 1996; SR-28391; Psyclone (Box 398)
          Catalog # BEF-0104; A-side Matrix # BEF-0104-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 15142
          Beat Force Recordings
        - Puazze Crew - Puazze show (Disc one), 1999; SR-28392; Puazze Crew; Sha One (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28393. Double album.
          Catalog # BNLP002; A-side Matrix # BNLP 002 1 A 33RPM
          Black Needle
        - Puazze Crew / Luce, Joel - Puazze show (Disc two), 1999; SR-28393; Puazze Crew; Luce, Joel; La Fuossera; Knut (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28392. Double album.
          Catalog # BNLP002; A-side Matrix # BNLP 002 2 A 33RPM
        - Public Announcement - Too hot, 1994; SR-28394; Public Announcement (Box 398)
          Catalog # DMD 2155; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-73457-73458-1 HFM cg
          Packetown
        - Public Announcement - Too hot, 1994; SR-28395; Public Announcement (Box 398)
        - Public Demand - Invisible, 1996; SR-28396; Public Demand (Box 398)
          Catalog # SAM 1916; A-side Matrix # SAM1916A1
          ZTT
        - Public Enemy - Poison remixes, 1999; SR-28397; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # PIASX014P; A-side Matrix # PIASX014P A1-1-1 John P
          [PIAS] Recordings
        - Public Enemy - It takes a nation of millions to hold us back, 1988; SR-28398; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # BFS 44303; A-side Matrix # BFW 44303-A-C1 G4 MASTERDISK DMM
        - Public Enemy - Resurrection, 1998; SR-28399; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # Def 234-1; A-side Matrix # DEF-234-1A RE-1 STERLING
        - Public Enemy - Brothers gonna work it out, 1990; SR-28400; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 44-73391; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK XSS-73391A-1A G1 DMM
        - Public Enemy - 911 is a joke, 1990; SR-28401; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 44-73179; A-side Matrix # XS-73179A-1A G1 MASTERDISK DMM C5
        - Public Enemy - Bring the noise (no noise version), 1987; SR-28402; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 651335 6; A-side Matrix # 651335-6-A-1
        - Public Enemy - Yo! Bum rush the show, 1987; SR-28403; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 450482 1; A-side Matrix # 450482-1 A1 TOWNHOUSE
        - Public Enemy - You're gonna get yours; Rebel without a pause, 1987; SR-28404; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 44 06861; A-side Matrix # XSS-176095-1A G1 MASTERDISK
        - Public Enemy - Fear of a Black planet, 1990; SR-28405; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # C 45413; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK DMM AL-45413-1A G1 B3
        - Public Enemy - Muse sick-n-hour mess age (Disc one), 1994; SR-28406; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28407. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 523 362-1; A-side Matrix # HFM 94 314-523-376-1AS
        - Public Enemy - Muse sick-n-hour mess age (Disc two), 1994; SR-28407; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28406. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 523 362-1; A-side Matrix # HFM 94 314-523-377-1-AS
        - Public Enemy - Welcome to the Terrordome; Shut 'em down, 2003; SR-28408; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # PRDJ7101; A-side Matrix # PRDJ101 A
        - Public Enemy - Nighttrain, 1992; SR-28409; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # XPR 1743; A-side Matrix # XPR 1743 A
        - Public Enemy - He got game (Disc one), 1998; SR-28410; Public Enemy; Masta Killa; KRS-One (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28411. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 558 130-1; A-side Matrix # STERLING 314-558-158-1A
        - Public Enemy - He got game (Disc two), 1998; SR-28411; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28410. Double album.
          Catalog # 314 558 130-1; A-side Matrix # STERLING 314-558-159-1A
        - Public Enemy - What kind of power we got?, 1994; SR-28412; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 422-853-939-1; A-side Matrix # 422-853-939-A-1 HFM cg
        - Public Enemy - Shut em down, 1991; SR-28413; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 44 74165; A-side Matrix # XSS-74165-B-1H
        - Public Enemy - Muse sick-n-hour mess age (Disc one), 1994; SR-28414; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28415. Double album.
          Catalog # 523 362-1; A-side Matrix # 523-362-1A/1
        - Public Enemy - Muse sick-n-hour mess age (Disc two), 1994; SR-28415; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          In same jacket as # SR-28414. Double album.
          Catalog # 523 362-1; A-side Matrix # 523-362-1 C/1
        - Public Enemy - Can't do nuttin' for ya man, 1990; SR-28416; Public Enemy (Box 398)
          Catalog # 656385 6; A-side Matrix # 6563856 A1
        - Public Image Ltd. - This is what you want...this is what you get, 1984; SR-28417; Public Image Ltd. (Box 398)
          Catalog # 60365-1; A-side Matrix # 1-1 ST-E-60365A-1
        - Public Image Ltd. - 9, 1989; SR-28418; Public Image Ltd. (Box 398)
          Catalog # 1-91062; A-side Matrix # ST-VR-897357-B 1-1
        - Public Image Ltd. - Seattle, 1987; SR-28419; Public Image Ltd. (Box 398)
          Catalog # DMD 1120; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-53195-1 Precision 1-1
        - Public Image Ltd. - Album, 1986; SR-28420; Public Image Ltd. (Box 398)
          Catalog # 60438-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60438-A-1 MASTERDISK 1-1
        - Publik Anounsa - Comin' from Crooklyn jointz, 1995; SR-28421; Publik Anounsa (Box 398)
          Catalog # U/NR003; A-side Matrix # U/NR003AN
          Upreyes Records
        - Publik Anounsa - Comin' from Crooklyn jointz, 1995; SR-28422; Publik Anounsa (Box 398)
        - Pucali - Ooh, right there, 1998; SR-28423; Pucali (Box 398)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # 5806-JUNK2-1A S 41183
          Blak Majiktives Pub.
        - Pucho - Tough!, 1966; SR-28424; Pucho; Latin Souls Brothers (Box 398)
          Catalog # PR 7471; A-side Matrix # DMC-3901 A-1/8-88
          Prestige
        - Puddu Varano - Blue sky white sand, 2002; SR-28425; Puddu Varano; Lady Z; Raw Deal Remix (Box 398)
          Catalog # Murena 014; A-side Matrix # MURENA014A-1
          Murena Records
          Denmark
        - Puente, Tito - Ran kan kan, 1999; SR-28426; Puente, Tito; Tañon, Olga (Box 398)
          Catalog # ED 6198; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-6197A-1
        - Puerto Rock - Bang out, 2000; SR-28427; Puerto Rock (Box 399)
          Catalog # AED 45588; A-side Matrix # XSS-45588-A-1B MASTERDISK
        - Puerto Rock - Burn it up, 2000; SR-28428; Puerto Rock (Box 399)
          Catalog # 7404; A-side Matrix # EPIC 7404-A Puerto Rock DCHARLES
        - Puff Daddy - Can't nobody hold me down (remix), 1997; SR-28429; Puff Daddy; Diddy (Box 399)
          Catalog # 78612-79081-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79081-1-SA-REI SP1 HFM 97 CSB
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - P. Diddy/Diddy - Bad boy for life, 2001; SR-28430; P. Diddy; Diddy; Black Rob; Curry, Mark (Box 399)
          Catalog # 78612-79400-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79400-15A RJ STERLING
        - P. Diddy/Diddy - Bad boy for life, 2001; SR-28431; P. Diddy; Diddy; Black Rob; Curry, Mark (Box 399)
        - Puff Daddy & the Family - Victory (remix), 1998; SR-28432; Puff Daddy & the Family; Puff Daddy; Diddy; Busta Rhymes; Notorious B.I.G. (Box 399)
          Catalog # BBDP-9158; A-side Matrix # BBDP-9158-SA
        - Puff Daddy/Diddy - Come with me, 1998; SR-28433; Puff Daddy; Diddy; Jimmy Page (Box 399)
          Catalog # COME W/ ME; A-side Matrix # EMC PUFFY DADDY "COME W/ ME"-A DCHARLES
        - Diddy - Get off, 2006; SR-28434; Diddy (Box 399)
          Catalog # PR 302363; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302363/302364A1 RJ STERLING
        - Diddy - Last night, 2006; SR-28435; Diddy; Cole, Keyshia (Box 399)
          Catalog # PR 302440; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302440A-1 RJ STERLING
        - Diddy - Come to me; Get off, 2006; SR-28436; Diddy; Scherzinger, Nicole (Box 399)
          Catalog # PR 302339; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-302339A-1 RJ STERLING
        - Pulse - Don't stop the magic, 1981; SR-28437; Pulse (Box 399)
          Catalog # SCO 6; A-side Matrix # SCO-6-A
          Silver Cloud Records, Inc.
        - Pulse 8 - Radio Morocco, 1990; SR-28438; Pulse 8; Jah Wobble; Adams, Justin (Box 399)
          Catalog # 440 504-0 DJ; A-side Matrix # 162-440-504-0-A 1-1 STERLING
          4th & Broadway ‎
        - Pump! - Disco bumper EP!, 1999; SR-28439; Pump!; Edenflux; DJ Nitro (Box 399)
          Catalog # BD0033; A-side Matrix # L-10000m-B BD-0033-B
          Bettery Day Records
          Louisville, Kentucky
        - Pump Blenders - Funk the people live, 1985; SR-28440; Pump Blenders (Box 399)
          Catalog # CHR 1501; A-side Matrix # CHR 1501A//2 420 P
          Cooltempo
        - Pump Blenders - Shake it, 1986; SR-28441; Pump Blenders (Box 399)
          In same jacket as # SR-28442. 2 copies.
          Catalog # F-0019; A-side Matrix # F-0019-A
        - Pump Blenders - Shake it, 1986; SR-28442; Pump Blenders (Box 399)
          In same jacket as # SR-28441. 2 copies.
        - Pump Boys - Pump me tonight, 1991; SR-28443; Pump Boys (Box 399)
          Catalog # RA 103; A-side Matrix # RA 103A SUNSHINE-FRANKIE"T"
          Rama Records
        - Pump Factory - Bat jam, 1989; SR-28444; Pump Factory (Box 399)
          Catalog # WAR-050; A-side Matrix # WAR-050-A F/W 1-1 CSB
        - Pumpkin - Here comes that beat!, 1984; SR-28445; Pumpkin; Profile All-Stars (Box 399)
          Catalog # PRO-7047; A-side Matrix # HERBIE Jr "Those BEAT'S "B" Fresh" A-1 PRO-7047-A
        - Punk Barbarians - Bubblin'; Platinum, 1996; SR-28446; Punk Barbarians (Box 399)
          Catalog # LET 6001-1; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK TD LET-6001+A
          Lethal Records
        - Punk Barbarians - Sex, props, cream... and the drama in between, 1996; SR-28447; Punk Barbarians (Box 399)
          Catalog # LET0001-1; A-side Matrix # LET-0001-1-A
        - Punk Barbarians - Blast off, 1996; SR-28448; Punk Barbarians (Box 399)
          Catalog # LET6002-1; A-side Matrix # MASTERDISK TD LET6002+1-A
        - Puppets - The way of life, 1983; SR-28449; Puppets (Box 399)
          Catalog # QUS 055; A-side Matrix # QUS-005-A STERLING
        - Puppets of Chaos - Tru dat; New & improved, 1995; SR-28450; Puppets of Chaos (Box 399)
          Catalog # PA-323-1; A-side Matrix # "The FIRST of MANY: PRO AMP ENT" PA-323-A (RE) 1-1 DCHARLES
          Pro-Amp Entertainment
        - Puppies - Summer delight, 1994; SR-28451; Puppies (Box 399)
          Catalog # 42 77724; A-side Matrix # XSS 77724A-1A
          Chaos Recordings
        - Puppies - Funky Y-2-C, 1994; SR-28452; Puppies (Box 399)
          Catalog # 42 77462; A-side Matrix # XSS 77462A-1A
        - Puppies - Funky Y-2-C, 1994; SR-28453; Puppies (Box 399)
        - Purdie, Bernard - Master drummers volume one, 1993; SR-28454; Purdie, Bernard (Box 399)
          Catalog # URLP 002; A-side Matrix # (T) URLP-002 A1 34150(2)
          Ubiquity
        - Pure Elegance - Keep ya movin (Disc one), 1996; SR-28455; Pure Elegance (Box 399)
          In same jacket as # SR-28456; SR-28457. Triple album.
          Catalog # PA1021-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1021-1-A EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 14566
        - Pure Elegance - Keep ya movin (Disc two), 1996; SR-28456; Pure Elegance (Box 399)
          In same jacket as # SR-28455; SR-28457. Triple album. Annotated.
          Catalog # PA1021-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1021-1-C EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 14566
        - Pure Elegance - Keep ya movin (Disc three), 1996; SR-28457; Pure Elegance (Box 399)
          In same jacket as # SR-28455; SR-28456. Triple album. Annotated.
          Catalog # PA1021-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1021-1-E EUROPADISK DMM NY USA 14566
        - Pure Energy - One hot night, 1984; SR-28458; Pure Energy; Stevens, Lisa (Box 399)
          Catalog # PRO 204; A-side Matrix # A1 ITP-204-A FW/NY
          Prism